[music]
My name is Batis Adul. I'm a senior
underwriting consultant and I work
specifically in the risk management
team. What I do is audit. We audit uh
the decision that were taken on policies
uh our process as well as our tools and
then we try to improve and make
suggestion to make things better and
always better for the client to be uh
this company that can bring some comfort
to the client. It's something that I
don't think has a price on it knowing
that your your family will be okay. The
thing that I like the most is the
communication and the collaboration. We
have a team that's not afraid to tackle
new tasks. I can always count on
somebody to to help me. I love working
at at Manual Life for many different
reason. Uh and one of them is the
opportunities that are endless here and
the training that is provided here. The
tool that they give you to be successful
at your job is priceless in my opinion.
My best advice would be if you come
here, come with an open mind and don't
be afraid to to tackle [music] new
challenges cuz change happen and change
is good.